Okay, let's do this!
Let's go!
Grr!
Quit screwing around and start!
The ambiguous 3cm?
Does that mean it's plushy? Wait!
The wrapping is a uniform, argh,
it's not an act, pooh
Gotta do your best, gotta just do it
That's time to catch 'n' release, eek
Between sweat (whoop)
sweat (whoop)
Darlin', darlin', freeze!
Kinda lethargic,
something's kinda comin' out
I love you... Oh wait,
one of those was different
Worrywarts, high metal bars
Tasty thoughts... And that's enough!
The heated body of that
flying you-know-who
It's what you call a normal girlie
Am I the only one surprised?
Seconds on pork-bone broth ramen
with wire-hard noodles
Da da da da da
Pom-poms cheer squad
Let's get cherry pie
Happy fun welcoming party
Look up! Sensation
Yeah! Feeling of existence,
dot dot small planet
Collided and it melted away,
in total awe
Go all out to sing, shi-ranger!
Take it away!
I should be the one who'll be
laughing in the end
Because I have the sailor suit
<- This is my conclusion
It's only Monday!
Already in a bad mood? What to do?
I really prefer the summer outfits
<- kya! wah! good! (cute!) <3
Until we approach 3 pixels,
no hesitations please *
Do your best, be energetic
My darlin', darlin' please!
Come to think of it, we're wearing
the summer uniforms starting today.
I bet Konata will still come
in the winter uniform.
There's always at least one person
in every class that forgets.
Morning, Sis!
Wow, there was someone
so close to me.
Oh, no, I forgot to apply for
the giveaway in The Tele!
Darn, I was kinda going after
that apron from Love Apron...
You just didn't have enough love.
You didn't have enough love,
Kagami, so you forgot.
Well, I was really busy lately
with the committee stuff
and studying for exams...
No, no, those are only excuses.
I've never forgotten, not even once!
Don't compare me to you!
You only think of playing around!
Or rather, how you phrased it
just now is really irritating.
How do you win those
giveaways, anyway?
In one word: Love!
Fine, I'm a woman with no love!
Well, if you send in a normal postcard,
you'll lose where you otherwise
stood a chance of winning.
How do you write your
postcards, Kona-chan?
Oh, I make them to win, of course!
How?
Neat handwriting is the
most basic of fundamentals.
You have to write a postcard
that the choosers
would just want to
get into their hands.
For example?
For example, use a highlighter to
draw a border on the postcard.
Oh, that really shows up well.
Furthermore, you add an illustration,
with a motif of the item
that you want to get.
An illustration?
I don't think I can draw very well.
People of that sort resort to numbers,
and send in many cards.
I think I can do that.
However, even when
you're submitting a lot,
don't use a printer.
You have to make sure to write
each and every one by hand.
And send a hundred at once.
A hundred?!
A hundred is like normal.
That costs a fortune!
It's so that you can
get what you want.
You need both enthusiasm
and investment.
But isn't there a time when
it's cheaper to just buy it?
There are things in this world
that money can't buy.
A hundred postcards...
Do they fit in a mailbox?
You don't put them in all at once,
but you send them in small portions,
a few at a time.
And you have to spread it
over several days.
When you have a lot of cards at once,
the chooser might
shove all of them aside.
Well, there are times when it's best
to not be so desperate,
and times when the opposite is true.
Then what should I do?
That's why it's all about love!
Whatever...
In any case, if you want
to win something,
check out free handouts or flyers
folded into newspapers as well,
and apply for something that
doesn't look too popular.
Chances of winning
are pretty high then.
Yeah, I'll try that.
Where's the love in that?
Kagami, Tsukasa... You sure
don't look alike, for being twins.
Oh, we're fraternal twins.
So the difference is more
like ordinary sisters.
Identical twins come from one egg
and really do look alike,
but fraternal twins can be different
in appearance and personality.
I see.
It's true that Tsukasa is so laid-back,
but Kagami is vicious.
- What was that?!
- Oh, how scary.
Maybe if we set your hairdo
and ribbons in the same way,
you might look more alike
than we think.
Kona-chan!
No good, it's impossible to put
something cute on you, Kagami.
Shut up! Don't go imagining
something on your own
and saying something rude from it!
Do you have something
like telepathy?
You know, how twins can be far apart,
but somehow they have
the same lifestyle habits
or same taste in the opposite gender,
and even marry other twins and stuff.
That, and like when one is in danger,
the other can sense it from
somewhere completely different.
There are all sorts of strange
phenomenon out there.
So you have telepathy
or something, right?
How about you try it out right now.
Like, beep-beep-beep.
That's just you reading
too much manga.
Mana-Kana, too...
Mana-Kana?
Both of them were saying how
they were slightly different.
Like how Mana's the one
who's really cautious,
and Kana's the one who's optimistic.
And they said their voices were
slightly different when they sing.
That reminds me,
Mana-Kana had always thought
that they were fraternal twins,
but they recently found out that
they actually were identical.
Really?
But is that something to be
so surprised about?
The definition of identical and
fraternal twins changed recently.
That means there's
the possibility that you two
are identical twins as well,
Kagami, Tsukasa...
The similarities between you two...
Both of you like sweets, right?
Yeah, I love them.
Sort of.
Both of you are left-handed.
- Yeah.
- That's right.
What's your favorite color?
White, I guess.
- Black.
- The same colors as your souls.
What was that?!
You know, with all this talk of eggs
and sausage, I'm getting hungry.
We weren't talking about food.
It's so muggy.
We end up sweating as soon
as it gets a little crowded.
It's getting to be
that time of the year.
It's hot!
They haven't turned on
the air conditioning yet.
Hold on!
It's hot!
Dear Soujirou and Konata Izumi,
We have not nurtured our love for so long,
but we, Kiyotaka Narumi and Yui Kobayakawa,
are getting married this coming XXth of June.
Dear Soujirou and Konata Izumi,
We have not nurtured our love for so long,
but we, Kiyotaka Narumi and Yui Kobayakawa,
are getting married this coming XXth of June.
The ladybug samba, punk version...
One of my relatives is
getting married this month.
Wow, a June Bride! That's so nice!
Why is such a wet,
gloomy season
the forerunner of happiness?
Um...
Why is it joyful to
get married in June?
Yeah.
They say that the term June
originates from the goddess
Juno in Roman mythology.
Juno is known as Hera
in Greek mythology,
and oversees marriages
and childbirth.
So, they say that those that
get married in the month of Hera,
namely June, are protected
and blessed by the goddess.
But Hera is Zeus's wife, right?
Yes, that's right.
I have an image of Hera
being a very jealous woman,
so to me, it doesn't feel really happy.
In a wedding, which would you like
to wear, a dress, or a kimono?
I would like to wear a dress.
It's what I've been dreaming of
ever since I was little.
I would have to say a dress as well...
But a kimono is nice too, after all...
I think I'd like to wear both.
I hear that as of late,
there are miniskirt versions,
and all sorts of colorful
wedding dresses.
I see... Miniskirt wedding dresses...
If it has a very frilly-edged design,
that might be really cute.
"I have many dreams,
I want a lot of frills," you know?
Tsukasa is like Angel Salvia.
No, from your hairdo
you're more like Daisy.
So the top should be yellow,
and the skirt should be a miniskirt!
Tsukasa-san would look good
in a miniskirt.
You think so?
The outfit is important,
but what kind of person
you marry is also important.
A childhood friend,
or a girl from a rich family.
It's hard to decide on which one.
On one end, you have a huge dowry.
You can use magic like
Beho#mi or l#nazun.
But, feeling-wise...
Bianca, no doubt about it.
Hey, Kagami, you're much
more pure than I thought.
I thought you'd run for
the girl with the money.
You didn't have a comeback ready?
S'up, Konata.
There was a place I didn't get in
that game I borrowed the other day.
Whoa, wait a minute, Kagamin.
Isn't it fun because you solve
things like that on your own?
You have a point.
Yup, yup.
In other words, you understand
the meaning of doing things yourself,
so you'll now do all your own
homework, right, Konata?
Detectives in manga and drama shows
keep running into murders,
for some strange reason.
Like Conan and Kindaichi.
If they didn't, the story
wouldn't go anywhere, right?
You think so? I think
normal cases would work too.
Normal?
Like running all over Japan
in search of a missing person.
I think following someone has
a highly game-like aspect.
It has thrill, and suspense.
Well, yeah...
Like accepting a request
from a husband to check out
whether or not his wife
is having an affair.
Or looking for lost pets?
Yeah, that's it.
But would you enjoy watching
something like that?
No, most likely it wouldn't be
any fun at all.
See?
That, and cases that happen in reality
usually don't use clever tricks
like those in manga or TV.
It's true that they don't.
Like faking a fingerprint,
or fabricating something,
or eliminating Luminol responses...
Like spoofing even the
forensic investigation team.
Well, those that are really tough
get copycat criminals,
so there's probably
some media censorship.
Oh, that...
Those perfect crimes end
without the public knowing,
or remain unsolved, huh...
That's a risky line, in all sorts of ways.
Don't you hate how there's
so much rain lately?
You're right.
I used to like the rain
when I was little, too...
Rain gets you wet,
and your laundry can't get dry,
so I never really liked it.
Kona-chan, why did
you like it so much?
Because rain would cancel
the baseball broadcasts,
so I could watch my anime
like I normally do.
I see. That's really like you
to say that, Kona-chan.
But nowadays, there are
so many domed stadiums...
Lucky Star!
What's wrong?
Often in manga, you have
really stupid characters
and really smart characters
attending the same school.
That's enough outta you!
Shut up! Gourds at the top
of the vine should stay out!
When you think about it,
it's really strange.
When you talk about that,
I just saw this anime recently,
where the teacher and
the students are the same age,
no matter how you thought about it.
Or rather, the teacher
actually looked younger!
Ma'am...
What is it, Miss Ta_____ana?
It's a well-known fact that
no matter who you are,
people like to see the gap between
actual age and physical age.
I don't get it.
You shouldn't doubt it.
Or rather, it's all the more
strange to have students
with different school scores
in the same class!
You're right. I really have
to agree on that part.
I hate to say this, but I'm surprised
that you actually got accepted
to this school, Konata.
You're good at cramming,
so maybe you did the same
for your entrance exam?
What? Is that really the case?
Well, it took more than
one night of studying.
You surprised me!
But I'm surprised that you
were able to keep studying.
Is there an entrance exam prep
game for the DS or something?
Dad gave me a couple conditions.
Like, a Pippin for a rank D school,
a 3DO for a rank C school,
and a PS2 for a rank B school.
Izumi's dad really knows how
to control his daughter.
I had a thought.
I'm even more surprised that
Tsukasa got into our school.
Shouldn't it have been a little harder
for you to say that?!
- All right! I won again!
- Damn, I can't win
if it's a fighting game.
- All right! I won again!
- Damn, I can't win
if it's a fighting game.
She's put too much time into them.
You can try me at anything,
even if it's not a fighting game.
Oh, is that right?
Then, next up...
I challenge you to a quiz game!
You're kidding!
I lost against Konata
in a game of wits?!
I can't believe this...
Can it be... that she memorized
the question patterns?
When it comes to games,
her memory's always top-notch!
What shall we play next?
Don't rummage through
stuff without asking.
Huh? That's strange...
You used to have a really
easy party game, right?
Why do you know which
games someone has?
That was something that even you
would be able to win, Kagami.
It was so smelly...
Kagami, you haven't eaten
any sweets for a while now.
You usually eat so much.
There's no real reason.
Oh, I get it! You're dieting
to get ready for the summer?
It's nothing like that.
You don't even have someone
to show off your bathing suit to!
Shut up! You don't need to go there!
By the way, you two were born
on the Star Festival day, right?
It's almost your birthday now.
Yeah, so?
Kona-chan, you remembered!
Seventeen years old, huh...
Seventeen is the year
before the unlucky year.
What happens in the year
before your unlucky year?
It's the year where unlucky
things start to happen,
right before your true unlucky year.
I see.
As my birthday gets closer and
closer, I get more uncertain,
so I ended up buying all sorts
of goods to ward off evil,
and power stones, and stuff like that.
That kinda sounds like fun.
Right. As I kept buying,
it kinda became...
Or rather, we have that
Alert Misfortune charm...
Oh, wait, it was the
Avoid Misfortune charm.
Alert misfortune, huh...
Like, "That's enough.
Safe childbirth, safe driving,
let's look all over all of it," and stuff?
Whatever...
Oh, that's right.
Did you know that your birthdays
are on Ponytail Day?
No, I didn't know that.
But why is it July 7?
It's said that Orihime in the
Star Festival legend had a ponytail.
That's really farfetched...
There really is a Japan
Ponytail Association,
and they give out the Japan
Ponytail Awards every year
to a celebrity that looks
good in a pontytail.
Oh, is that so?
But I think anyone would
look good in a ponytail.
I wonder.
I have the shortest hair,
so it's really cutting it close.
But a small ponytail looks cute.
Kona-chan, you look good too.
I think you'd be okay like that
in everyday life.
You think so?
Yeah, I think so.
You too, Sis...
Kagami, you're...
It's okay. Fine.
I should just take it off.
You look so manly, like a samurai.
Well, excuse me!
You know how drunks usually wrap
their neckties around their head?
Is there any meaning behind that?
Oh, that?
Isn't that like when
they loosen their ties,
and it got stuck while they were
trying to pull it off their heads?
I see.
If you're going to say that,
I think people
who always carry takeout boxes
are more unnatural.
Takeout boxes?
Those boxes that Kato-chan
carries in the Drifters shows.
I don't think I get it.
Even now, the image of a drunk guy
is always with a tie around his head
and carrying a takeout box.
I don't know why...
Me neither!
I hope Orihime and Hikoboshi
can see each other this year...
Twinkle, twinkle...
And I hope that Alert Misfortune
charm will have good results.
That's a needless worry.
Right now the Comp-Fest is in the
middle of a QUO-card giveaway.
Come to think of it, you
always collect QUO-cards,
but do you ever use them?
I don't use them.
Then why do you bother?
Don't you blindly want goods from
your favorites when they come out?
As a fan, and as a collector.
I don't know, cards
that you never use?
You can't use it! You have
to safely stow it away.
When I see people carelessly
using them, it really pisses me off.
Items like this should never be used!
And auctioning or selling them off
is out of the question.
If you do, of course you fail as a fan,
but you also fail as a collector!
You say it so passionately, but...
In my case, I need
at least three cards.
One to keep for eternity,
and I safely stow it away
in a special case just for it.
And one to pull out and
look at every so often.
What about the third one?
- To spread the gospel.
- What's with that?
When you really want something,
don't you want to have two
or three of them, Kagami?
Yeah, yeah, you don't.
Fine, I'm an otaku. I'm strange.
No, I vaguely understand
what you're trying to get at.
Tsukasa, you look like the type
that would be popular with boys,
but I never hear anything like that.
Tsukasa is a bit plain, and
she doesn't really stand out.
Yeah...
Maybe it's because a scary-looking
sister is always guarding her?
Did you say something?
I think it's not that I'm plain,
but more like Kona-chan and
Yuki-chan are very unique.
Miyuki-san really knows
a lot of stuff, and is pretty,
and has a nice figure, and really
wears glasses out of necessity,
- and hates dentists, and is clumsy,
and is a natural airhead...
- Hey now,
- and hates dentists, and is clumsy,
and is a natural airhead...
didn't that get a bit
strange in the middle?
But, come to think of it, there
aren't any rumors about Miyuki.
Maybe guys find it hard to approach
her because she's so pretty?
I don't think that's the case.
She's so nice, and
looks out for others so well.
You're right.
Maybe she's been asked out a lot.
But she's saying no?
She's saying no, huh...
Or when someone asks her out, she
doesn't realize she's being asked out.
That might be it.
Yuki-chan tends to be a bit dense,
so guys have to tell her in
a very straightforward way.
Really, the boys in your class
are all so irresponsible.
Doesn't somebody in there
have enough guts
to passionately state his feelings
and woo Miyuki?!
I don't think there is.
Maybe we don't have that many
maniac-types in our class.
A girl like Miyuki-san is
a little more geared
towards the maniac-types.
A maniac-type, huh...
Oh, it's already this late?
If you'll excuse me now...
Already?
Oh, please don't mind me,
and continue to relax.
Then, excuse me...
Yeah, see you later!
Laters!
And, there was more
to that story, and he...
Excuse me!
All right!
I'm sorry...
No, no, no...
It happens! I've done it before too.
I have too.
Everyone does it at least once.
You've done it too, right, Konata?
Nope.
In other words, that's
one part of her moe!
Miyuki-san...
Good job!
Lucky Star!
Lucky Channel!
Morning Luckies!
Yeah, today, we're starting
Lucky Channel again
with squeak-squeak-squeaky energy!
I'm Akira Kogami,
your navigator! And...
Well, I'm Minoru Shiraishi,
assistant to Akira-sama.
Nice to see you all.
Right, right...
It's already the third time that
the two of us have run the show!
What do you think, Shiraishi-san?
Have you gotten used to it yet?
No, not really... I'm sorry.
Well, it seems like you really haven't
opened up your heart
to me yet, Shiraishi-san...
It seems like you're sitting a bit
further away from me than usual.
Maybe this is the distance
between our hearts...
That's not the case, really...
Now, I'd like to start with
a twinkle again today!
Let's see... Today is a very
happy project for all fans!
Can you believe it?
The introduction of the Lucky Star
regular cast, first installment!
Yes. Today, we are introducing
Miss Miyuki Takara.
Let's see... Class committee chair,
beautiful appearance,
gentle-spirited, obviously intelligent...
That's "clearly intelligent".
Clearly,
good at literature and athletics,
a perfect superhuman...
Shiraishi-san, you know
a lot about Miyuki, right?
Oh, I know a lot about her!
Miyuki is very nice.
First off, those glasses!
And she's really pretty.
Usually, when someone
is that beautiful,
you get the feeling that you
shouldn't be going near her,
- but she turns out to be
very easygoing and friendly...
- Wow...
- but she turns out to be
very easygoing and friendly...
I wish you would talk
that much on the radio.
I see... Get you started on Miyuki,
and you can't stop.
Oh, no, it's nothing like that...
Well, yeah... Was it
Miss Miyuki Takara?
She's one of those
pretty-faced characters?
And she's got big breasts?
And even her faults just
make her more moe?
- I'm so jealous...
Those beauty-type pretty women
- Akira-sama, are you there?
- I'm so jealous...
Those beauty-type pretty women
are also liked by the
maniac-types too...
But when it comes to being
liked by the maniac-types,
well, I have all the pedo...
Oh, too bad!
It's time to say goodbye already!
And so, in this segment, we always
seek questions and praise for me,
as well as your opinions of the show,
so please send them!
Oh, then... Please look
forward to next time.
See you!
So what is she actually like?
She's just like how I described her.
You're kidding! She's not puffing out
white smoke from her nose
in the dressing room or something?
Oh, on that point she's fine,
she's not like you, Akira-sama.
I see.
That's amusing.
That was a unique song.
I'd like to hear a song that is
easy on ordinary people's ears.
You'll know the next song, Kagami.
Let's guess what it is from the intro!
I hope this isn't another strange song.
Oh? What was this?
I don't know...
And, Kagamin, what's the answer?
Oh, it's Full Metal!
Full Metal?
Furthermore, it's Kagami's
favorite, Fumoffu!
So that's it.
I just read the novel a bit,
and was only slightly hooked!